[Siren]
危险第三情
You once said, talking aboutyour childhood,
你曾经在谈到你的童年时讲道
"I grew up with seriousness all around me. "
“我的成长历程是非常的严肃的”
Yeah. My parents were very, very strict.
是的，我的父母对我非常非常的严格
He thinks I put up 1 00,000
他认为我提供了100,000美元
to watch it go down the toilet?
然后眼睁睁的看着它掉进马桶
He doesn't care aboutyour money.
他毫不在意你的钱
I want him to know it's every cent I've got.
我只是想让他知道这每一分钱都是我挣来的
It represents pocket change.
它代表了一种微小的转变
I can't get hit harder.
我无法接受比这更大的打击
Does he know what this can do to me and Karen?
他知道这对于我和凯伦来说是什么吗？
I knowyou're out there.
我知道你在外面
Does he know it?
他知道吗？
Michael...
迈克尔…
Listen, Roger, that does it.
听着，罗杰，就这样
Sounds good. Fax it to me.
听起来不错，传真给我
I'll look at it, talk to you tomorrow.
我先看看，明天再和你联系
I tried to keep it quiet.
抱歉，我试着安静点
I heard a noise from downstairs.
我在楼下就听到了吵杂的声音
Didn'tyou hear it?
你不觉得吗？
No. I was on the phone with Roger.
不，我再和罗杰打电话
It's probably the wind,
可能是风吧
Fuzzface here.
毛掉到脸上了
Why does he hate me?
为什么他讨厌我呢？
Ifyou paid more attention to him,
要是你对他多关心一点
he'd likeyou better.
他便会多喜欢你一些
Ifl fed him goodies likeyou do.
要是我像你一样给他为糖果吃
I thinkyou're jealous ofTiny.
我觉得你妒嫉泰尼
Of course. He sleeps with you more often.
当然，他更经常和你一起睡呀
Is that...
是…
Um, I'll go down.
呃，我下去看看
Maybe we should call the police.
也许我们应该叫警察来
No, that's O.K.
不用，行了
I'll just check it out.
我去检查检查
Don't worry. Ifit's anything serious,
别担心，要是出事的话
I'll come back for my driver.
我会回来拿我的起子
Michael, is everything all right?
迈克尔，都还好吗？
There's somebody in the house.
有人在屋子里
Call the police.
报警
Michael!
迈克尔！
No!
不！
Stop it.
别动
Stop!
别动！
Stop, motherfucker!
别动，妈的！
Back off.
后退
Back off!.
后退！
O.K.
OK
Drop it! Drop--drop it!
扔掉，扔…扔掉！
Drop it.
扔掉
Drop it!
扔掉！
Just take anything you want, all right?
想拿什么就拿好了，行吗？
You can have mywatch.
给你我的手表
I don't want that goddamn watch.
我不要那该死的表
Please don't hurt her.
别伤害她
I'll giveyou anything you want.
我给你你要的一切
Aah!
啊！
Karen!
凯伦！
Police, sir.
是警察，先生
Hi. Come on in, guys.
嗨！进来吧，老兄
Hi. I'm Officer Cole.
嗨！我是柯尔警官
This is my partner Officer Davis.
这是我的搭档戴维警官
Mike, how are you?
迈克！还好吧？
What happened to your foot?
你得脚怎么了？
I knocked a beer bottle down in the kitchen.
我在厨房把啤酒瓶摔碎了
I stepped in it. It's nothing, really.
我进去，没事儿的，真的！
So, Mr. Carr, can you tell us what happened?
那么，卡尔先生，你能告诉我们发生了什么吗？
Yeah. We were, uh, we were upstairs in my office,
当然，我们，呃，我们在楼上我的办公室里
mywife and I,
我妻子和我
and we, uh, heard a noise.
我们，呃，听到些声音
This is mywife Karen.
这是我的妻子凯伦
Thanks for coming so quickly.
谢谢你们这么快赶到
What happened after you heard the noise?
你听到声音然后怎么了？
Michael went down, and I--I, uh...
迈克尔就下楼去，我…我…呃…
I--I heard another noise.
我…我听到另外一个声音
I went down, and, uh...
我下了楼，呃…
It's O.K., Mrs. Carr.
很好，卡尔夫人
Just take your time.
别着急
Well, this man jumped out ofthe closet,
嗯，那人就跳出了衣橱
and he and Michael fought.
他和迈克尔打了起来
It wasn't much ofa fight, really.
也不算是打了，其实
I just grabbed his leg.
我只是抱住了他的腿
Hewas trying to get away.
他想逃走
Got out in the kitchen.
出了厨房
He got ahold of Karen and went out back.
他抓住了凯伦然后就出去
He put a knife to her throat.
他把刀架在她的喉咙上
You O.K.?
你还好吗？
Yes.
还好
You need a doctor?
需要看医生吗？
No.
不用
You sure?
你确信？
Yeah, thanks.
确信，谢谢
Tiny.
泰尼
Tiny?
泰尼？
Come here, Tiny.
过来，泰尼
Not a very good watch cat, are you, Tiny?
不是一只很好看的猫，对吗，泰尼？
[Michael] He's useless.
他没什么好处的
Well, I guess he likes policemen.
恩，我猜他喜欢警察
We'll have someone over in the morning to dust for prints.
我们上午会叫人来擦掉上面的印迹
Try and not disturb too much.
希望不会打搅到你们
We've had several break-ins in this area lately.
最近在这个地区我们都发现几起入室案件了
We're pretty sure it's the same guy.
我们相当确信这是同一个人干的
On this street?
都在这条街上？
In this general area, but we'll get him.
大概这片区域，但是我们会抓到他的
Wouldn't mind being there forthat.
不必担心他会再来这儿了
Does anybodywant coffee?
你们要喝咖啡吗？
Yes. I never turn down coffee.
对啊，我从不拒绝咖啡
Whoa! Watch--
当心！看…
Watch the glass.
看有玻璃
Oh.
噢
Excuse me.
抱歉
Thanks.
谢谢
Ifthis guy's been doing this around here,
要使这个人以前在这附近犯过案
is there any chance he's going to come back?
他有可能还会来吗？
We were told this was a safe neighborhood.
据说这儿是个安全的地方
All things considered, Mrs. Carr,
卡尔夫人，据我们看来
this is a safe neighborhood.
这儿是个安全的区域
Mr. Carr probably scared the hell out ofthe guy,
卡尔先生都已经吓走了那人
so he won't come back.
所以他不会回来的
I'm getting a gun.
我要去买支枪
What?
什么？
No guns in this house.
这屋子里不许有枪
Maybe she'll listen toyou guys.
或许她会听你们的
Don't get a gun.
别买枪
You can say that. You've got one.
你当然这样讲了，你已经有一支了
And I'm trained to use it.
我在接受训练，学习该怎么用
I've done some shooting.
我开过枪
At targets.
是对靶子
Not people.
不是对人
Look, take our advice.
看，采纳我们的的意见吧
Get an alarm.
买个警报
Get a dog. Forget about guns.
买只狗，别去想枪了
The wrong people always get hurt.
人们经常被误伤
Nice people.
多好的人
Hey, I know what you're thinking.
嘿！我知道你在想什么
What--what am I thinking, Roy?
什么…我在想什么，罗伊？
[Karen] I'm never going to be able to sleep.
我睡不着
[Michael] Me, either.
我也是
I thought he--
我想，他…
When he grabbed me, I thought...
当他抓住我，我想…
It's all right.
好了
I don't think I can stay here, Michael.
我认为我不能呆在这儿了，迈克尔
It's just so weird.
好怪异
We'll get some things together
我们收拾好东西
and go to a hotel.
去旅馆
No. I mean I don't think I can live here anymore.
不，我的意思是我不能再在这儿住下去
I thinkwe should sell the house.
我觉得我们应该卖掉这房子
Wait. You love this house.
等等，你喜欢这房子
I know, butwe really don't need this.
我知道，但是我们真的不需要这房子了
Slow down.
且慢
Michael,
迈克尔
we're in way over our heads.
我们脑袋里都乱了
We can barely afford this place.
我几乎不能够再忍受这个地方
Don't get carried away.
别乱想了
Know what we're going to do?
知道我们现在应该做什么吗？
We're going to take that cop's advice.
我们应该采纳警察的意见
Tomorrow morning I'll make a few phone calls.
明天早上我要打几个电话
We'll get the best security system known to man, all right?
我们去购置最好的安全系统，好吗？
Ifthat doesn't do it, we'll just--we'll--
要还不行的话，我们只好…我们就…
We'll get a killerwatchdog.
我们就买只狗看家
I mean, a vicious...
我的意思是，要一只恶犬…
pit bull...
强壮的…
with fangs...
有很锋利的牙齿…
with a studded collar.
带上一个带上装饰钉的项圈…
Come on, honey.
来吧，甜心
We'll be all right.
我们会好的
Come on.
来吧
You chased him around with a fucking putter?
你就拿着那该死的高尔夫球杆追他？
You're a hero.
你真是个英雄
Dirty Harry and Arnold Palmer
卑鄙的恶魔和阿诺德・帕默
all wrapped into one, that's me.
汇集于一体，就是我
Sounds pretty intense.
听起来相当刺激
With me, boom. Heart attack. Done.
和我一起，轰隆，致命一击，搞定
You did O.K. You guys all right?
你干得很棒，你们都还好吗？
Yeah. Well, Karen's upset.
还好，嗯，凯伦有些心烦
Shit. Here he comes.
狗屁，他来了
We have to kiss him?
我们难道需要吻他吗？
Gentlemen.
先生们
I read your prospectus. Demographics look good.
我看了你们的样书，人口学看起来很棒
Well, I'll tell you,Jerry.
嗯，我要告诉你，杰里
I'm not a big believer in demographics.
我不是人口学的忠实信徒
It's a lawyer's tool.
那是律师们的工具
No offense, Roger.
不去进攻，罗杰
None taken.
就没有收获
Quite an amazing place.
好一个令人吃惊的地方
The potential here's fantastic, huh?
这儿的潜能有些奇怪，嗯？
I've learned to go with my instincts.
我按照本能学着去做
The one time I used demographics,
我第一次使用人口学
I went belly up.
快把胃给吐了出来
That wasn't Denver, was it?
那不是丹佛，对吗？
He's done his homework.
他已经完成了作业
You weren't the only one.
你不是唯一的一个
I put a lot of my clients' money there.
我把我许多客户的钱都放在那儿
All those buildings are still empty.
那些建筑物都还是空着
That won't happen here.
这儿不会有那种事情
This downtown area has undergone
这个市中心地区已经经历了
some amazing revitalization.
一些令人吃惊的复兴
Those new buildings over the last 1 0 years?
在过去10年里？那些新建筑
All filled with people,
里面都挤满了人
all within shouting distance ofthis place here.
所有的都在离这儿不远的距离
O.K. Here's what I want to do,
OK，这就是我想做的东西
whatworked the other three times.
在其他的三个年代里都起了作用
Put on a backers' party--
搞个支持者的聚会…
It's mine.
是我的
Hello.
喂！
Hi. It's me.
嗨！是我
Hey.
嘿
Bad timing?
停工时间？
We're in the middle ofit, butwe're getting close.
我们在里面，但是我们变得很亲切
What's going on?
怎么了？
Those security people haven't shown upyet,
那些负责安全的人还没有来
neither have the police to dust for prints.
警察也还没有擦掉印迹
Did you call?
你打了电话？
Yeah. All I get is the runaround.
对啊，我听到的都是借口
Great. I'll tell you what.
好的，我要告诉你什么
Here's whatyou do.
就是你要做的
Call the police.
报警
Ask to talk to those cops from last night.
从昨晚开始，就要求和那些警察谈话
Those guys can help, O.K.?
那些人还是有用的，知道吗？
O.K. I'll try.
好吧！我试试看
I'll be home soon. You all right?
我马上就要回家了，你还好吗？
Uh-huh.
还好
You sure?
你确信？
I loveyou. Bye.
我爱你，拜！
Michael, this guy's good.
迈克尔，那人很好
I'm being grilled here.
我对这儿很感兴趣
Michael, this area's high-crime.
迈克尔，这个地区是高犯罪区
Soyou get people in.
那你让人进来
How doyou keep the bad element out?
你怎么能排除掉坏的因素呢？
I'm into that as we speak.
我们谈着谈着就谈到了点子上
I'm working on security right now.
现在我在做有关担保权的事情
Ha ha ha!
哈哈哈！
Michael, you remember Officer Davis?
迈克尔，你还记得戴维警官吗？
Oh, yeah. Howyou doing?
噢，记得你要干什么？
I didn't recognizeyou out of uniform.
你穿制服我都没法认出你
You did all this?
这一切你做的？
It's no big deal.
小事情一桩
It is. We appreciate it.
干得很好，我很欣赏
It's the least I could do.
我还能做更多的事情
Mrs. Carr called my captain
卡尔夫人叫我队长
and said nice things about me and my partner.
对我和我的搭档说了好多好话
Usually people call to bitch.
通常人们叫做婊子
Itwas nice. I'm grateful.
很好，我很感激
Can I getyou something?
我能给你什么吗?
Sure. Thatwould be great.
当然，太好了
- Great. - Thanks.
- 太好了 - 谢谢
There's going to be contact switches
要接触到开关
on every point of entry.
在进入室内的每一各地方上
A breeze won't get into this house
微风也吹不进房间
withoutyou knowing it.
让你觉察不到
Hereyou'll have an infrared motion detector.
这儿你要装个红外线探测仪
This right here will be tripped
要是有人打破玻璃
ifanybody breaks the glass.
恰好在这儿就会被发现
Hey, w-what's he doing in the bathroom here?
嘿！他…他在洗澡间里干什么？
Oh.
噢
Um...
嗯…
It's--it's just an extra precaution.
那是…那是个额外的防范
It's a safe room.
这是个安全的房间
These old houses are great
这些老房子很好
because the doors are like solid rock!
因为门都坚固得像岩石
We put a heavy dead bolt on each entrance here.
我们在每个入口都装上了很死的门闩
In case there's an intruder,
万一有谁破门而入
you lockyourselfin and wait for the cavalry,
你把自己锁好，然后等待骑兵救援
which is us.
我们就是骑兵
You just have to pick out a code word now.
你现在需要挑选一个密码
It's got to be seven letters.
需要7个字母
Pyramid.
Pyramid
Pyramid?
Pyramid？
Uh, this is the Michael Carr residence,
嗯，这是迈克尔・卡尔的住处
and the code word's going to be "pyramid."
密码是“Pyramid”
Right.
正确
O.K. Thankyou.
OK！谢谢
That's it.
就这样
Oh, yeah.
噢，好的
440 cubes, 500 horses.
440立方，500马力
Jesus.
我的天
You do the workyourself?
你自己做的？
Uh-huh. Every nut and bolt.
对的，每一颗螺丝都是
Installed the alarm. Relaxes me.
安装警报，令自己舒服
That is nice, really nice.
很好，真得很棒
Thanks.
谢谢
You got a knack for this security stuff.
你找到了这些安全材料的诀窍
Did you ever think about consulting as a sideline?
你有没有考虑过兼职做咨询？
Consulting?
咨询？
Yeah.
对
Homes, businesses.
家庭的，商业的
I got a club I'm putting together downtown.
我有个俱乐部，我要把它搬到市区里来
It's whatyou're doing today,
这就是今天你要做的
butyou get paid foryour time.
但是你都拿到了今天的薪水
I never thought about it.
我从没有想过
Staying for dinner?
留下来吃饭吧？
Yeah.
好的
- You doing anything? - Not tonight.
- 你有什么需要做吗？ - 今晚上什么也不做
I'd be crossing the line--
我正在跨越一条线…
Cops on one side, everybody else on the other.
警察在一边，其他人在一边…
Come on in.
来吧
This has really been nice.
这真是太好了
Usually, dinner for me
通常，晚餐对于我来说
is a bunch of us sitting around
就是让我们坐在一起
boring each other with war stories.
给对方讲战争故事
That's why cops stick together.
这就是警察老缠在一块的原因
Nobody else could stand us.
没有其他人能支持我们
You've never been married?
你还没结婚？
No. Nope.
不，没有
She'll try to lineyou up with one ofher friends.
她正试图使你成为她的一个朋友
I'll get her,Jack!
我要得到她，杰克！
Sorry, Michael.
抱歉，迈克尔
She smells that meat and goes crazy.
她闻了那肉快疯掉了
Meet me around the front.
在前面附近等我
I'm sorry. I'm still a little freaked.
抱歉，我还是有些反常
That's O.K.
没关系的
That's understandable.
可以理解
I can't believeyou've never been serious about anyone.
我不能相信你从来没有对谁认真过
No.
没有
Cops and marriage are a tough combination.
警察和婚姻是一个牢固地结合体
I can't believe how much I'm talking.
我无法相信当我还是小孩子的时候
When I was a kid, I hardly ever talked.
我能讲出多少，我几乎不谈这个
When I was in school, I never talked.
我上学时从没谈过
I was famous for it.
我这方面很好
Oh, well, take it from a teacher.
噢，嗯，在老师面前很好
We love those quiet little boys
还是小孩，我们就喜欢
in the back ofthe class.
在课后谈论
Don'tyou believe her, Pete.
你难道不相信她，皮特
She loves all kids.
她喜欢小孩
Oh, that's what's missing.
噢，这就是怀念的东西
I'm surprised you two
我对你们俩感到很吃惊
don't have a few running around.
别老是徘徊
Michael, I'm--I'm sorry about bringing up kids.
迈克尔，我…我对带孩子的事情很抱歉
That's really none of my business.
真的不关我的事儿
I justwanted to thankyou.
我只想感谢你
You reallywent out ofyourway.
你真的要走自己的路
I can't tell you whatyou did for Karen.
我无法告诉你你为凯伦做了什么
She'll bounce back.
她会恢复过来的
She'll bounce back quicker because ofyou.
她因为你，会快些恢复过来的
What aboutyou? Haveyou bounced back?
你呢？你恢复过来了吗？
I don't know.
我不知道
Guy gets his hands on yourwife like that,
伙计，像这样把他的手交给你的妻子
you feel pretty helpless.
你感到很无助
You did whatyou could.
你尽了全力
You showed a lot ofballs
你向那人展示了许多
going up against that guy.
即将发生的东西
There was one moment there where, uh,
那一刻，嗯，
he had ahold ofher,
他抓住了她
and I had that stupid golf club,
我却拿着那该死的高尔夫球棍
but I thought I could just--
但我想，我只要…
I didn't--didn't take the shot.
我不…我不能让他开枪
A fucking nightmare when you think
当我想象她可能会怎么样的时候
about what could've happened to her.
真是他妈的一场噩梦
I wouldn't mind one more shot
我不会介意对那婊子养的
at that son ofa bitch.
多开一枪
Really?
真的？
Hell, yeah.
该死的！对
I'd like to kick the shit out ofhim.
我真他妈想踢他
I'm sureyou would.
我确信你也会的
Wouldn'tyou?
你难道不会吗？
I already know what I would do.
我已经知道我应该做什么了
I was justwondering
我就只是在犹豫
about a nice civilized guy likeyou.
一个像你一样的有礼的人
Afterwhat he did to Karen,
他那样对凯伦后
I think all the rules are out thewindow.
我把所有的规则都抛到了窗外
I'd rip his fuckin' heart out.
我他妈要撕开他的心
Michael.
迈克尔
You're a scary guy.
你是个容易慌的人
Hey...
嘿…
You know,
你知道
I betyou'd enjoy coming on a ride-along.
我想你一定想独自开开车
What's that?
什么？
Ride along with us on patrol one night.
和我们去巡逻一晚吧
You can do that?
你们要巡逻？
We do it all the time forwriters,journalists.
我们为了作家，为了记者，整天干这事儿
Yeah. That sounds--
好的，听起来…
Yeah. I could do that.
嗯，我愿意
I'm going to set it up.
我去准备一下
Comewatch us kick some butt.
过来看我踢靶垛
When?
什么时候？
Tomorrow.
明天
Ugh.
唷
Come on.
来吧
It'll be fun.
很有趣的
Yeah.
好的
Why not?
一定来
Great. I'll seeyou then.
太好了，到时候见
Sign this soyour old lady can't come after the city
在这上面签字，你那老女人就不会跟着来城市了
ifyou get killed, maimed, or dismembered.
要是你被杀了，弄残了，或者肢解了
Nothing will happen to him.
对他没有任何影响
He's with me.
他和我在一起
Hey, Pete.
嘿，皮特
O.K., Mike,
OK，迈克
a dope dealer, a public defender, and my ex-wife
一个毒贩，一个公设辩护者还有我的不合法的妻子
all get thrown off the Empire State Building.
都将被扔出帝国政府大厦
Which one hits the cement first?
哪一个先落到地上？
I don't know.
不知道
Who lands first?
谁先着陆？
- Who cares?
- 谁关心呢？
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, my gosh.
噢，噢，噢，噢，噢，噢，噢，唉！…
Look at this.
看这个
Think she's a real blonde, Roy?
我认为她是一个真正的金发碧眼的美女，罗伊对吧？
Officer...
警官…
was I going too fast?
我是不是开得太快了？
Mm-hmm.
嗯
Doyou have a license and a registration, ma'am?
你有驾照和注册证明吗，女士？
Yes.
有
Certain types ofwomen just have a thing for cops.
各种类型的女人对警察来讲都是一样
They think we're like movie stars.
他们认为我们像电影明星
We ever search any one ofthese assholes here,
我们调查过这儿所有的混混
we'd be up to our butts in drugs and guns.
我们现在的目标是要调查毒品和枪支
This place is one giant supermarket ofshit.
这个地方是他妈一个巨大的超市
Isn't that right, Leon?
你很好吧，里昂？
Whateveryou say, Officer.
你怎么说都对，警官！
I ain't into nothing.
我什么都不是
This is Mr. Clean.
这是克林先生
That's right. That's me.
行了，是我
Yes, sir. Mr. Clean.
是，长官！克林先生
Maria, como esta?
玛丽亚，科莫埃斯塔
Bien.
比恩
Everything O.K.?
一切都好吧？
It's O.K.
都好
No problemos?
没问题吧？
No. Noproblemas.
没，没问题
Ifthere is, you let me know, O.K.?
要是有问题，告诉我，好吗？
All right.
好的
I don't thinkyou'll be finding any clientele
我觉得你为你的俱乐部在这儿…
foryour club around here, Michael.
找不到客户，迈克尔
Try it.
试试看吧
Best in L.A.
洛杉矶最好的了
You know, I ate before I came out.
你知道，出来之前我吃过了
I'm reallyfull.
我真的不饿
So...
那么…
you enjoying yourself?
你高兴吗？
Yeah. Yeah. It's an eye-opener.
高兴，高兴呀，大开眼界
Something occurred to me
我遇到了一件事
when you were over at the house
当你们们在那边房子前
for the barbecue, Pete.
买烤肉的时候，皮特
I don't know how it works in Los Angeles,
我不知道在洛杉矶是怎么的
but when I was in Phoenix and Kansas City,
但是当我在菲尼克斯和堪萨斯城
I hired off-duty police officers
我雇用了离职警官
to work the club.
到俱乐部工作
Hear that? Mike's offering us moonlighting money.
听到了吗？迈克要提供我们兼职机会
I'd like to talk about it.
我要谈谈这个
Hi.
嗨
So how areyou?
呃，你们好吗？
Areyou, like, the captain or something?
你们像是队长或者其他什么的，是吗？
Lieutenant.
中尉
Rosa...
罗萨…
Come on. Vamonos.
来吧，瓦莫诺斯
Can'tyou see the lieutenant's a married man?
你看不出这个中尉已经结了婚了吗？
Oh, yeah?
噢，是吗？
Oh.
噢
Oh, well.
噢，好吧
Te amo, Roy.
特阿莫，罗伊
Bye, Pete.
拜，皮特
[Pete] See you later, Rosa.
下次见，罗莎
These bitches can't get enough of us.
这些婊子在我们这儿得不到满足
Michael, stay here.
迈克尔，呆在这儿
Keep away.
让开
Police. Everything all right in there?
警察，里面都好吧？
No! Everything isn't all right!
不，出事儿了
Fucking asshole hitJim in the face!
那个妈的混帐朝吉姆脸上打了一拳
Fuckyou!
操你妈！
In the fucking face!
他妈的打在脸上！
Shut up!
闭嘴！
Thereyou go.
你们去那儿
You all right?
你还好吧？
Attaboy.
好啊
Just stay here with me
和我就呆在这儿
and hang on for a second.
逗留几分钟
Roy, I'll take him now.
罗伊，我现在要带走他
Take that piece of shit back to the jailhouse
带那帮混蛋们回监狱去
where he belongs!
他们就该呆在监狱！
Aah!
啊！
Mom!
妈妈！
Mommy!
妈咪！
See? They got him.
看到了吗？他们抓到他了
Why don'tyou go up and getyourself cleaned up?
为什么你不上去洗一下呢？
Me and Mike will put the car to bed.
我和迈克去停车
Works for me.
帮我一把
Later, gentlemen.
稍等，先生
Take care.
小心
It's a hell ofa life, huh, Mike?
真是人生苦境，嗯，迈克？
Is it always like this?
总像这样吗？
Oh, yeah. Day in and day out.
噢，对的，每天进进出出
Hop up in front.
上前去
Uh, yeah.
嗯，好的
And yourwife wants to know
你妻子想知道
why I can't meet a nice woman.
为什么我不能遇到一个好女人
You guys handled it all prettywell.
你们这些家伙处理得相当好
Listen, where are we headed?
听着，我们去哪儿？
Just got one more errand to run.
只要找件事去做就行了
Come on!
来吧！
Move!
走啊！
Michael!
迈克尔！
- Aah! - [Thud]
啊！
Stay there.
呆在这儿
Michael, meet Ernie Pike.
迈克尔，和恩尼・派克碰头
Come out and I.D. This piece of shit.
出来，身份证给我，该死的家伙
Come on, motherfucker!
快呀！操你妈
Hey, that's him!
嘿！就是他！
You got him.
你抓了他
Goddamn it! That's him!
该死的！是他！
Did you hear that? You just been made.
听到了吗？就是你做的
You just been made, scumbag!
就是你做的，卑鄙的家伙！
Picked up a crackhead pal ofhis.
抓住那帮人的头目
Turned in Pike here.
带到派克这儿来
You broke into my friend's house?
你闯入了我朋友家中？
Huh?
嗯？
Did you scare him and his prettywife?
你吓到他和他美丽的妻子了是吗？
Did you do that?
是吗？是你做的吗？
O.K. I'm sorry, man.
对，抱歉，老兄
O.K.?
行了吧？
Shut the fuck up!
你他妈的闭嘴！
He doesn't want to hear aboutyou being sorry.
他不想听到你说抱歉
He wants to kickyour ass,
他想踢你屁股
and guess what, scumbag?
猜猜然后呢，该死的家伙！
I'm going to let him.
我要让他来了
[Pete] Ready?
准备好了？
What?
什么？
What areyou waiting for? Let's go.
你还等什么？走
Areyou serious?
你认真的吗？
Yeah, I'm serious.
对，我认真的
You said you wanted
你说你想要
to rip his fucking heart out.
掏出他的心
Well, yeah, but I mean, that was, you know--
嗯，对，但是我的意思是，你知道，那…
I was just talking.
我只是说说而已的
Tell him.
告诉他
Say it. Say howyou wanted that uptown pussy.
说， 说你怎么想要什么，臭B！
Say it!
说！
Is that what you wanted? Say it!
这就是你想要的？说！
Say it!
说呀！
O.K. I...
好，我…
Tell him!
告诉他！
Whateveryou say, man.
你说什么都行，老兄
Whateveryou say.
你说什么都行
Come here.
过来
Don't you fucking resist me.
你他妈别再和我作对
Don't you resist me!
别再和我作对！
Now walk.
现在就走
I said walk.
我说走
He just gaveyou the O.K.
他就对你说了个“行了吧”
Here. You don't even have to touch him.
拿去，你不用碰他了
I wasn't going to hurt nobody, man.
我不想伤害任何人，老兄
Shut up.
闭嘴
Come on.
过来
Come on, Michael.
过来，迈克尔
It's O.K. Listen.
很好，听着
He resisted. He gets hit.
他反抗，他欠扁
Shit happens.
他做了些什么
Come on, Pete. Y-you got him.
过来，皮特，他交给你了
Nice going. Let's take him in.
干得很好，让他进去吧
Michael, he put a knife to Karen's throat.
迈克尔，他把刀架在凯伦的脖子上
You're going to let him get awaywith that?
你就让他那样走了？
Hit the motherfucker!
揍他呀！
Pete.
皮特
Hit him! Hit him!
揍他，揍他
No. I'm not doing this.
不，我不会这样做
Hey!
嘿！
Aah!
啊！
Motherfucker!
该死的家伙！
Aah! Aah!
啊！啊！
Hey, Pete!
嘿，皮特！
Pete! Jesus, that's enough!
皮特！天哪，够了！
Honey?
亲爱的？
Michael?
迈克尔？
Yeah. It's me.
对，是我
How'd it go?
怎么样了？
Boy, what a screwed-up night.
孩子，多迷人的夜晚
What happened?
发生什么事情了？
Ah, it was just-- It was weird.
啊，只是…有点怪
I went with the guys on a few calls,
我和那些家伙一起拜访了几处地方
got to watch them be cops.
去看他们怎么做警察
Then we dropped Roy off,
然后我们离开了罗伊
and Pete had a little surprise for me.
皮特使我有些吃惊
The guywho broke in here.
那个破门而入的家伙
He caught him?
他抓到他了？
He did more than that.
他还做了很多
The guy's in jail.
那人进监狱了
Hospital's more likely.
更有可能是在医院
He really beat the living shit out ofthis guy,
他真地把那家伙打了个半死
which is what I was supposed to do.
本来我想动手的
What?
什么？
Petewas showing offfor me.
皮特为了我而大打出手
Had thewhole thing set up
仿佛所有的事情都解决了
so I could nail the guy.
所以我不会再盯着那个家伙
I'm just glad it's over.
我只是为解决了这件事情而高兴
Yeah.
对
Areyou sure you're O.K.?
你确信你还好？
What's the matter?
发生什么事儿了？
I just...
我只是…
I think our cop friend
我觉得我们的警察朋友
is a little too tightly wound, that's all.
好像也受了点伤，就这个
Well, doyou thinkyou might be overreacting a little bit?
嗯，你觉得你可能有点反映过度吗？
Not really.
没有觉得
You know, I feel like a big weight's been lifted.
你知道的，我感觉就好像试举起了沉重的东西
Yeah. Well, I'm glad you feel better, honey,
对的，嗯，我很高兴你感觉还好，宝贝
but I don't want him around here anymore.
但是我不想他会再来这儿
Honey, you're upset. I understand.
宝贝，你有些困惑，我知道
But shouldn't we give him
但是我们难道不能对他…
the benefit ofthe doubt?
有个好一些的怀疑吗？
You're acting like Pete's the criminal.
你的行为好象皮特是罪犯似的
Oh, am I?
哦，是么？
I was there, Karen. I saw it, O.K.?
凯伦，我在那儿，我看见了，知道吗？
I don't care whatyou think.
我不管你怎么想
You don't care what I think.
你也不用关心我怎么想
Fine. I won't bother thinking.
好吧，我不再干涉你的想法
Knock it off.
停下来
No, you knock it off!.
不，你停下来！
I'm sorry, but I don't shareyour sympathy
我很抱歉，但是我不赞成你对那人的同情
for the man who broke in and put a knife to my throat!
他破门而入还用刀架在我的脖子上！
Hi. Uh, sorry.
嗨！呃，抱歉
I didn't mean to scareyou.
我不想吓着你
That's O.K.
还好
Can I talk toyou for a minute, please?
我能和你谈谈吗？
Just let me get my robe, all right?
让我穿上衣服，好吗？
You know, you really should put a lock on that gate.
你知道，你真的应该在门上放一把锁
I don't thinkyou came here to discuss my gate.
我认为你来这儿不是谈论我的门
No.
不是
Did you hear I arrested the burglar?
你知道了我逮捕了夜贼
What happened?
发生什么事情了？
What happened was,
出现的状况是
the burglar knocked me down
夜贼将我击倒
and took off running,
想跑
and when I caught him, he resisted,
当我抓住他时，他反抗了
and it--it got ugly.
然后…然后就变得不堪设想
I don't think Michael took it too well.
我认为迈克尔不容易接受
He didn't quite put it that way.
他不会那样处理的
It's not a TV show out there, Mrs. Carr.
这不是一个电视节目，卡尔夫人
The reality gets to people
人们知道了事实
who've never seen it up close like that.
他们没有设身处地地经历这一切
You mean the violence.
你是说暴力
Look...
你看…
When I first started out,
当我首先动身的时候
uh, I went on a routine call.
嗯，我继续程序调入
All right?
行吗？
It was a young kid. He was high on drugs.
那是个小孩，他吸毒成瘾
He was beating on his girlfriend.
他在打他的女朋友
She couldn't have been more than 1 5, 1 6.
她可能还不到15或者16岁
Sweet girl-- blond hair, blue eyes,
很甜的小女孩…金发，兰眼
so I didn't pay her much attention.
所以我对她没怎么留意
I was reading the kid his rights
我当时给小孩讲他的权利
when she took out a gun
那是她却拿出一支枪
and she shot me right here in the chest.
他朝我的前胸开了枪
So now I restrain felons first
所以现在我无论如何
with whatever it takes--
也无法克制当时那重罪…
Whatever it takes, and that's how it was last night.
无论如何，就是昨晚的一切
I don't need another bullet in the chest,
我不需要在胸前再挨一颗子弹
and you don't need a dead husband.
你也不需要一个死去的丈夫
I'm very sorry if Michael's upset.
要是迈克儿苦恼，我会很抱歉
I was just doing myjob.
我只是在做我的工作
Pete. Pete, wait.
皮特，皮特，等等
I--I'm...
我…我
I'm glad you got him.
我很高兴你抓到了他
That guy's not going to forget
那家伙不会忘记
the night he made the mistake ofbreaking in here.
那天晚上他闯入这儿所做的一切
That's for sure.
那是肯定的
O.K. Enjoyyour swim.
好了，你游泳吧！
This is the chromalite,
这是铬器,
and it serves as the backdrop
他用来做背景的
for the dance floor area here.
为这儿舞台地板区域做一个背景
With this chromalite, we can create any environment.
有了这个铬器，我们能创造环境
We've got cityscape here,
在这儿我们能欣赏都市风景
but this could be a desert or mountain. Anything.
但这可能是片沙漠或者是山地，任何东西
Yeow!
耶噢
I didn't know Michael had so many good-looking friends.
我不知道迈克儿还有这么多如此美丽的朋友
Are you kidding?
你开玩笑？
We don't know any ofthese people.
这些人我都不认识
They're all potential investors
它们是潜在的投资者
or friends of Michael's lawyer.
或是朋友，或者迈克尔的律师
That's too bad.
太糟糕了
Oh, now, there's one I'd like to meet.
噢，现在，是我想看到的那个
That's the guy I was telling you about.
那就是我给你谈到的人
Your cop?
你的警察？
Mmm.
嗯
Really?
真的？
Candace said the music's too loud.
坎迪斯说音乐太吵了
Who?
谁？
Candace. Mywife.
坎迪斯，我妻子
Roger, I got a question onlyyou can answer.
罗伊，我有个问题只有你能回答
I got an I RS auditor and a lawyer--
有个美国国税局审计员，还有个律师…
Another lawyerjoke.
另外一个律师的笑话
Divorce lawyer--jump off a building at the same time.
离婚案的律师…同时跳下楼房
Who lands first?
谁先落到地面？
- Who cares?
- 谁关心呢？
Hi. Howyou doing, Mike?
嗨，你怎么样，迈克？
Pete.
皮特
This place is great.
这地方真是太棒了
Thanks.
谢谢
Pete Davis. Los Angeles Police.
皮特・戴维，洛杉矶的警察
Hello, Pete. Jerry Lurie.
嗨，皮特，杰里・卢里
Excuse me.
抱歉
Jerry.
杰里
- Mywife Candace. - Hi, Pete.
- 我妻子坎迪斯 - 嗨，皮特
Roger Graham.
罗杰・格雷厄姆
Mike's been talking to me
迈克给我讲到过
about security for the club.
俱乐部的安全问题
Areyou working the area tonight?
你今晚在这片区域工作吗？
No. I did the precheck ofthe exterior.
不，我预先调查了一下外面
I know it's normal to have your entrance under the marquee,
我知道要你们从帐篷下进来是很平常的事儿
but it's too open. It's hard to control.
但是，它敞得太开了，很难有所控制
Be better to put the entrance in the alley.
最好把入口设在小巷里
Make people line up and file in.
让人们排着队进来
Ifthings get crazy and we have to get heavy,
要是情况疯狂起来，我们的责任不得不变大
only a few people will see it.
只有很少的人明白
Something to think about.
考虑考虑吧
Why don'tyou get yourselfa drink?
为什么不来杯饮料呢？
I'll be with you in a minute.
我一分钟后再来
Yeah. Good idea. I knowyou have business to discuss.
对啊，好主意，我知道你有生意要谈
I'll fill you in later. Take care.
我一会儿进来见你，保重
He makes a lot ofsense.
他太冒昧了
[Roger] Yeah.
是的
You guys aren't bullshitting.
你们没有说错
No. I take security very seriously.
不，我把安全问题看得很认真
Yeah. We're really on top ofit.
对的，我们真正应该重视
Hi, there.
嗨！那边儿…
Oh, Penny. This is Pete.
哦，彭尼，这是皮特
Pete, Penny.
皮特，彭尼
Hi, Penny. Nice meeting you.
嗨，彭尼，很高兴见到你
Hi. Nice meeting you.
嗨，很高兴见到你
We teach together.
我们在一起教书
Oh. Oh.
哦，哦
The kids at school would be so impressed
学校里的孩子们给人的印象是那么的深
I'm talking to a real policeman.
我正在和一位真正的警察谈话
They love cops.
他们喜欢警察
They'reyoung. Give them time.
他们还小，给他们些时间
Maybeyou'd like to come and give them a talk sometime.
或许什么时候你能来给他们讲点什么
Um...
呃…
Yeah. Sure.
好的，一定来
Public relations loves stufflike that.
考虑到公共关系应该这么做
Well, speaking ofpublic relations, doyou dance?
嗯，谈到公共关系，你跳舞吗？
Honey, can you rescue Roger-- Help me out?
宝贝，你能帮我救救罗杰出来吗？
Hey, Penny.
嘿，彭尼
Come on, Pete, let's get that drink.
来吧，皮特，我们来喝饮料
Here's toyour club, Mike.
这是你的俱乐部，迈克
Pete, uh, I want to get something straight here.
皮特，嗯，我想这儿整洁些
I'd likeyou to leave.
我想你离开这儿
Michael, what's with you tonight?
迈克尔，你今晚怎么了？
Why did you even invite me here?
为什么你居然邀请我来这儿？
Oh, no. Telling you and inviting you
噢，不，告诉你和邀请你…
are two completely different things.
是两个完全不同的概念
You seem so uptight.
你看起来很焦躁
Relax. Is it because you were up late last night?
放松点，是因为你昨晚睡得晚的原因吗？
How doyou know?
你怎么知道？
I was driving byyour house on patrol.
我开着车巡逻路过你的住处
I sawyour lights on till well after 3:00.
我看到你家的灯凌晨三点后才关掉
You don't have to protect us anymore. You caught him.
你不必再保护我们了，你已经抓到了他
You think that's it?
你这么认为？
You're not a virgin anymore.
你不再是个处男了
You saw how much evil shit's out there.
你在外面那儿看到了多少肮脏的东西
What kind offriend wouldn't try to protectyou and Karen?
哪种类型的朋友不想保护你和凯伦？
You listen to me 'cause I'm telling you--
你听听我的，因为我告诉你…
You leave us alone.
你离我们远点
You know, I think I understand
你知道，我认为我很明白
where this is coming from.
这是因为什么
Oh, doyou?
哦，是吗？
Yeah.Just cut the shit, O.K.?
是的，别他妈再说了，好吗？
Nobody expects you to be me.
没有人希望你来教我怎么做
I make my living going up against guys like Pike.
我工作就是和那帮家伙作对，就像派克
You don't. You've got nothing to be ashamed of.
你不是，你没什么可耻的
Is that whatyou think this is about?
这就是你所想的？
Yeah, I do.
是的，我这么认为
I betyou had one hell ofa night when you got home.
我赌你回家后有个糟糕的夜晚
A friend would be thanking me.
是朋友的话会感谢我的
I'm notyourfriend. I'm nothing toyou.
我不是你的朋友，我和你没任何关系
You're a sick guy.
你觉得你有病
I don'twantyou around me or mywife.
我不想你老是出现在我和我妻子身旁
Michael, your guests--
迈克儿，你的客人…
I'll be right there.
我马上去
Michael needs to get some things offhis chest.
迈克尔需要把心里的话说出来
- Michael, Roger-- - Honey, please.
- 迈克尔，罗杰… - 亲爱的，好了
Kicking me out, Michael?
把我赶出去啊，迈克尔！
Honey, please don't keep them waiting.
亲爱的，别让他们等
Ifl have to.
如果我必须这样做的话
Tell Roger I'll be there in a second, O.K.?
告诉罗杰我马上就去，好吗？
Everybody's free
∮所有的人都是自由的∮
To feel good
∮感觉很好∮
What are you going to do?
你要干什么？
You going to call the cops?
你去叫警察？
Get the fuck out!
滚出去！
Loweryour voice.
小声点
Fuckyou!
操！
- Loweryourvoice. - Fuckyou!
- 小声点 - 操！
Your pigeon's watching.
你的鸽子正看着
Hope he doesn't fly away on you.
希望他别飞走
Hey, need your car, man?
嘿，老兄，用一下你的车！
Ticket.
票子
Don'tyou think you were rough on Pete?
你不觉得我们对皮特太粗暴了吗？
I told you I don't want him around.
我告诉你我不想他再出现在我身边
I wanted to make that clear.
我想清爽点
Well, you succeeded.
好，你赢了
Come on, guys, it's time for our toast.
来吧，朋友们，吃土司了
Come on.
走吧
[Jerry] Uh, good health,
呃，好身体
good fortune,
有钱
and the time to enjoy it.
有时间享受
That's an old Castilian toast.
这就是古西班牙土司
Translated.
翻译了的
[Candace] Honey, looks like
亲爱的，你看起来好像
you've just made these two people very happy.
刚才使那两个人很高兴
[Roger] Candace, I know three people
坎迪斯，我认识三个人
your husband's made happy tonight.
你丈夫今晚使他们都很高兴
We'll all be happywhen everything falls into place, Roger.
罗杰，随着事情的发展，我们都会高兴的。
What's not to fall into place?
有什么事情不会出现呢？
That is a nice ride, dude.
车很棒啊，花花公子
[Michael] I thoughtyou were about to propose
我觉得你会推荐
another one ofthose wonderful continental toasts.
另外一个很棒的欧洲大陆土司
[Jerry] To the two most charming women here--
给那两个这儿最有魅力的女士…
Your beautiful wife and mine.
你美丽的妻子和我妻子
Ohh...
噢…
Mmm...
嗯…
I'm glad you called.
我很高兴你给我打电话
I been thinking aboutyou a lot lately.
我近来很想你
Leave it.
别碰
Sorry.
抱歉
Still sensitive, huh?
仍然很敏感，哈！
You get shot or something?
你中弹了，还是其他的什么？
Itwas a fishing accident.
是捕鱼时发生的事故
Yeah.
是的
Who fishes with guns?
谁用枪捕鱼？
Areyou all right?
你还好吗？
'Causewe can go to a motel
因为我们可以去汽车旅馆
on a nice, cozy bed.
在极爽的，舒适的大床上
I mean, ifyou're having a problem...
我的意思是，要是你有问题的话…
A problem?
问题？
The only problem that I have...
我唯一的问题就是…
is sleazy, lowlife whores likeyou.
太廉价了，像你一样的下等娼妓
That's my problem.
这就是我的问题
What the hell's wrong with you?
你究竟怎么了？
Get out.
出去
I'm not getting out here!
我不会出去的！
Just get the fuck out!
你他妈给我出去！
Areyou crazy? I don't know where the fuck I am.
你疯了吗？我不知道我他妈这是到哪儿来了
That's exactly your fucking problem, isn't it?
那很明显就是你他妈的问题，不是吗？
Isn't it?
不是吗？
So, being a policeman
所以，作为一个警察
is really all about helping people.
要真正帮助大家
It's about being a friend.
要成为大家的朋友
It's not about shooting it outwith bad guys.
而不是向那些混账开了枪就了事
That's what you see on TV.
那是你在电视里看到的
That's not why I wanted to become a cop.
这就是我为什么不做警察的原因
I became a cop to protect people--
我做警察，是为了保护民众
To make them feel happy and safe.
使他们感到高兴和安全
Everybody understand that?
你们都知道吗？
Yes.
知道
Does anybody have any questions?
还有人有疑义吗？
What?
什么？
Do you wear bulletproofvests?
你穿防弹背心吗？
Uh-huh. Have to to protect myself.
嗯哼，必须保护自己
Who else?
还有其他的吗？
In the police car,
在警车里
areyou always with somebody?
你总和其他人一起吗？
Mm-hmm. I have a partner named Officer Roy Cole.
嗯…我有个搭档就是罗伊・柯尔长官
We've worked together for the past 7, 8 years.
我们一起共事了七八年
He's a very good friend.
他是个很好的朋友
O.K. You.
好，你来…
Can you show me how to use your handcuffs?
能展示一下怎么使用手铐吗？
Ha ha ha.
哈哈哈
Sure. Come here.
当然可以，过来
What's your name?
你叫什么名字？
Matthew.
马泰
Matthew? All right, Matthew,
马泰？好的，马泰…
put your hands out.
伸出手来
Think I could get him to use those on me?
想象我让他用这个拷我？
Thereyou go.
你来吧
You're under arrest, Matthew.
你被捕了，马泰
Hi. I couldn't take off without saying thanks
嘿，我不能离开
for letting me impress the kids.
除非让我感谢你给我留下了孩子们的美好印象
That was really a lot offun.
这是真正的快乐
Penny really set it up.
彭尼真正动身了
Yeah. I talked to Penny before.
是的，我以前和彭尼讲过
I'd like to apologize for the other night.
我要道歉，为另一个晚上
Michael's behavior,
迈克尔的行为道歉
that kind oftook me by surprise.
那种让我吃惊的行为
I would've never shown up.
我不会再说了
Pete, it's notyou. It's him.
皮特，不是你，是他
He's just not been himselflately.
他最近不像他自己
Would you like to go get a cup of coffee?
你想来杯咖啡吗？
I--I don't go on for a while.
我…我暂时还不走
That's not a good idea.
不太好吧
You're safe with me. I'm a cop.
和我在一起很安全，我是警察
Just for a little while?
就一会儿？
Yeah.Just...
对，就…
Is everybody in here a cop?
这儿有警察吗？
Yeah, pretty much.
有，好多
About a year ago, some jerk came in here
大约一年前，一群性情怪异的人来到这儿
and tried to rip this place off.
试图捣乱
He didn't do too well.
他做的不是很棒
When he come crashing through the skylight,
当他彻底爬出天窗时
I say, " How's your dick?"
我说：“你鸡巴怎么了？”
I'm sorry. We should go somewhere else.
抱歉，我们应该到其他地方去
No. This is great.
不，这儿很好
Really?
真的？
Yeah.
对
I think it's really nice you got a place to go.
我觉得你找的地方很好
I'd like one.
我喜欢
Just--this is...
只是…这
this is my least favorite time ofthe day.
这是我那天最不高兴的时间
Why?
为什么？
Uh...well, 'cause it's getting dark out
呃…嗯，因为天已经黑了
and Michael's not homeyet.
迈克儿也还没有回家
How'd you and Michael get together?
你和迈克儿怎么会在一起的？
I was a waitress at his first club.
我在他第一个俱乐部作过侍者
Really? You were a waitress?
真的？你做过侍者？
It was the first job I ever had--
那是我的第一份工作…
The first one I needed.
我需要的第一份
We were kind ofwell-off.
我们关系很好
My father, as it turned out,
我父亲，正如看到的一样
had sort of a gambling problem, so...
有赌博的问题，因此…
You know, then people started coming over
你知道的，那时午夜时分，很多人过来
and taking our cars in the middle ofthe night.
开走了我们的车
It--it was kind ofa scary time.
那…那真是一种令人吃惊的情形
And Michael tookyou away from all that?
从那以后迈克儿带走了你？
Things always came really easilyto Michael.
对迈克尔来说，事情总是变得简单
Is thatwhy you married him?
这就是你为什么嫁给她的原因？
I married him because I fell in lovewith him.
我嫁给了他是因为我爱上了他
Hmmph.
恩呼
This is, uh...
这个，呃…
I hardly knowyou, and I'm talking like this.
我和你还不熟，就这样和你谈话
Karen, all the things that come so easilyto Michael--
凯伦，所有的事情对迈克尔来说都是如此简单
Wereyou one ofthem?
你也是其中之一吧？
'Cause there's no man that deserves that much good fortune.
因为没有人应该得到那么多的财富
I mean that.
我的意思是
A woman likeyou a man should never take for granted,
像你一样的女人，男人绝不应该对你随随便便的
and you should never feel unsafe.
你也不应该觉得不安全
And I wantyou to know
我想让你知道
that ifyou ever need anything--
要是你需要什么的话
You're feeling bad in anyway
无论怎么只要你感觉不好
oryou just need to talk--
或者你仅仅需要和人谈谈心…
That I'm there foryou, O.K.?
我会随叫随到，好吗？
As a friend... as a real friend,
作为一个朋友…一个真正的朋友
I'm there foryou.
我随叫随到
O.K.?
好吗？
Come on. Let me get you out ofhere.
来吧，我带你出去
How was your afternoon?
你下午怎么样？
Hey. Good.
嘿，很好
It was fine.
很好
You and Mrs. Carr getting along O.K.?
你和卡尔夫人相处得还好吧？
We seem to be.
似乎很好
When I was a kid at Erasmus,
在伊拉兹马斯，我还是个小孩时
I didn't have a single teacher that looked like Karen.
我没有像凯伦的单身老师
I mean, they all had blue hair
我的意思是，他们的头发都是蓝色的
with names like Mushbutt orSilvercrone.
名字就像是笑柄或者是希尔瓦老妪
Silvercrone's my maiden name.
希尔瓦老妪是我未婚时的名字
She had me.
她懂我了
Thankyou.
谢谢
The good news is
好的消息是
FrankTaft was so take with you,
弗兰克塔夫就那样被你带走了
he's considering kicking in halfthe capital himself.
他在想他可能自己踢到了头
FrankTaft? Booyoo Records?
弗兰克塔夫？布约里克孜？
Yeah. We handle him.
对，我们处理了他
There's a company that's on a roll.
名单上有个公司
Major roll.
成年人名单
The kids love it.
小孩们都喜欢
Excuse me, sir, I'm sorry.
请原谅，先生，我很抱歉
Doyou have another card?
你们还有另外一张卡吗？
What's the problem?
什么问题？
It's canceled.
这张作废了
That's impossible.
不可能的
Computer glitch. Happens to me all the time.
电脑故障，我经常发生
This is unbelievable.
难以置信
Relax. You'll get the next one.
别着急，你还会拿到一张的
Ifyou insist.
要是你执意
Don'tworry about it.
别为此而烦恼
All right. Now, we're on forTuesday night.
好的，呃，我们礼拜二晚上会到的
Bye.
拜！
Take care, Roger.
保重，罗杰！
Michael, what's that?
迈克儿，什么？
Looks likeyou're having a bad night, Michael.
看起来好像晚上你很倒霉，迈克尔
Look, all I know
听着，我知道
is what's on the computer print-out,
电脑输出了些什么
and the computer says you got parking tickets.
电脑说你收到了违规停车罚单了
And the computer is wrong,
电脑出问题了
so I'm not paying 600 bucks for tickets I didn't get.
所以我没有收到，我不用付那600元卖票的
I've worked here five years.
我在这儿工作五年了
The computer's neverwrong.
电脑从来没有出过错
Doyou want the boot off your car or not?
你还想不想要汽车的行李箱？
Ha ha. This is unbelievable.
哈哈，难以置信
Here.
这儿
Wait a minute. Not that one.
等等，不是那张
Honey, you sure about this?
宝贝，你确定？
Remember the night we went to the Minzers' house?
记得我们去明择的房子的那个晚上吗？
What?
什么？
They had the party on Canon Avenue.
他们在圣经大道上有个聚会
I got one ticket.
我得到了一张票
600 bucks? Come on.Jesus.
600元？来吧，我的天
Sorry, pal. You're over the limit on this card.
抱歉，帕尔，你的卡用光了
It's a computer thing, like Roger said.
就像罗杰说得那样，这是电脑问题
Yeah. Right.
对的，对
600 bucks.
600元
Oh, Michael, drop it, O.K.?
哦，迈克儿，扔了，好吗？
Things went prettywell, didn't they?
事情会变好的，对吧？
Yeah.
是的
I thought itwent pretty good.
我觉得会好的
You know what?
你知道什么？
It went great.
会很好的
You really charmed the pants offthe Luries.
你真的被卢里脱裤子吸引？
Oh, please.
噢，求求你了
Thanks.
谢谢
Stay here and lock the door.
呆在这儿，把门锁好
Michael, what are you doing?
迈克儿，你在做什么？
Karen, it's all right.
凯伦，很好
Hello.
喂！
Yes.
嗯
It's Michael Carr.
是迈克尔・卡尔
Uh, code word is pyramid.
呃，密码是pyramid.
Well, we just had our cat
嗯，刚刚是猫
knock over a screen is all.
撞翻了屏幕
Thankyou. Bye.
谢谢，再见
You know, I never thought I'd be so happy to see him.
你知道的，我从来不认为我见到他会高兴
Look, I thought it was the right thing to do.
看吧，我认为这就是要做的事情
Thanks for making that decision for both of us
感谢你为我们俩作出的决定
without my having a say.
我没给你讲过
Goddamn it, you know how I feel about those things.
妈的，你知道我是怎么摸索这些东西的
You know how I feel
你知道我有什么感受吗？
watching a man attack mywife
当我看到一个人袭击我的妻子
and I can't do anything about it?
而我当时又无可奈何
I'm not going to be in that position again.
我不想再处于那种状态下
I don't care what the police say.
我不管警察怎么讲
I'm keeping that gun.
我要留一支枪
I'm sorry. I should've told you.
抱歉，我应该告诉你的
You all right?
你还好吗？
Yeah.
嗯
Areyou?
是吗？
Aah!
呃！
Jesus Christ!
天哪！
Just a goddamn minute! Hey!
该死的时刻！嘿！
What the fuck areyou doing?
你他妈在做什么？
I was responding toyour alarm, Michael.
我在对你的报警作出反应，迈克尔
Bullshit! You tripped ityourself!.
狗屎！你自己的把戏吧
What?
什么？
The credit cards, the boot on my car--
信用卡，我车上的行李箱
You did that, too, didn'tyou?
你还干了这些，恩？
Everything all right in here?
这儿都还好？
False alarm.
假警报
False alarm, my ass.
假警报，我他妈的
I'm as embarrassed as you are.
我和你一样窘迫
Get the fuck out of my house!
你他妈给我滚出去！
I'm very sorry, Mrs. Carr.
很抱歉，卡尔夫人！
Oh, man. That son of a bitch is crazy.
哦，老兄，那婊子养的疯了
Hello.
喂
Yeah. Roger.
对，罗杰
Michael?
迈克儿？
I know it's late. I'm sorry.
我知道都晚了，很抱歉
Listen, how do I get a psycho cop off my back?
听着，怎么才能让警察离开我？
And you're the same Michael Carr
你还是那个迈克尔・卡尔
that I O.K.'d to do a ride-along
那个我批准过和
with Officer Davis and Officer Cole?
戴维警官还是柯尔警官开车的迈克尔？
Yes, sir. That's right.
是，先生，对的
The same Michael Carrwhose wife called to commend officer Davis?
迈克尔和他妻子还一样都在赞扬戴维警官
Yeah. The same two people
是的，同样的两个人
that are now being terrorized
都受过恐吓
by this out-of-control sicko.
被那个失去控制的精神病恐吓
Out-of-control sicko.
失去控制的精神病人
Sure there's nothing personal in this, Mr. Carr?
当然这不是个人的事情，卡尔先生
There's no question that it's personal.
不是私人的问题
What do you call it when an officer busts intoyour bedroom
当警察闯进你的卧室，你为什么打电话来？
whileyou're having sex with yourwife?
那时你在和你妻子做爱？
Yes, well...
嗯，对…
Officer Cole's report says
柯尔警官的报告写道
he and Officer Davis were responding to an alarm.
他和戴维警官去处理案件
That was verified byyour security company.
被安全局证实了的
Sure. How about the boot, my credit cards?
当然，行李箱怎么了？还有我的信用卡
What about them?
怎么了？
Got any proofthat this guy did those things?
有什么证据是那家伙干了这些事情吗？
You know, you're accusing a highly decorated officer.
你要知道，你在控诉一位高级警官
I don't care how many medals he has.
我不在意他得过多少勋章
I want this taken care of.
我想这些事情应该被注意到
Or else?
或者其他的什么？
You're not giving me anything.
你们没有提供我什么
You didn't bring any evidence.
你没有证据
You don't have anywitnesses,
你也没有证人
not even a home video.
甚至连家庭录影带也没有
These days, everybody's got a goddamn home video.
这年头，每个人都有家庭录影带
O.K. Fine. You're just going to bury this thing.
好，很好，你们想掩盖这件事情
Mr. Carr,
卡尔先生
this is a professional organization here,
这里是专业机构，
and we're going to do a professional investigation, O.K.?
我们在做的是专业调查，知道吗？
Mac, bring me the complaint forms, will you?
迈克，把投诉表给我，好吗？
Ifthere's anytruth toyour allegations, we'll take care ofit.
要是你的辩解有任何真相，我们会关心的
Thankyou.
谢谢
Department doesn'twant an unstable officer on the street
警局不希望街道上有办事不力的警官
any more than you do.
他们比你做得多些
Fill this out. You got a pen?
填填这个，你有笔吗？
No, sir.
没有，警官
Thankyou.
谢谢
Roger, how we doing?
罗杰，我们怎么做？
He's not coming.
他不会来了
Your friend Officer Davis called Lurie on the phone,
你的朋友戴维警官拜访了卢里
asking all kinds of questions--
问了各种各样的问题…
Does he knowyou? Has he done business with you?
他认识你吗？他和你做过生意吗？
Lurie's nervous enough to pull his people out.
卢里很烦，几乎要把所有人都赶出去
He thinks you're under some kind ofinvestigation.
他觉得你在接受某种调查
This fucker is ruining me.
这该死的毁了我
We're not dead yet. We have to deal with your friend.
我们还没死，我们还得处置你的朋友
I already filed a complaint.
我已经填好了投诉表
You're the one who told me to do it.
是你告诉我去那样做的
Michael, this is some kind of cop scam.
迈克尔，这是警察的某种诡计